[

](https://copyleaks.com/)

* Solutions
    * * * #### Solutions
                
        * * AI
                
                Insights
                
                The Original Source
                
                A Copyleaks Podcast
                
                Join host Shouvik Paul, COO of Copyleaks, and other members of the Copyleaks team, along with leading industry experts, as they update you on the latest in AI, EdTech, plagiarism, and more.

    * * * [Academic IntegrityThe only solution that detects AI-generated code, plagiarized and modified source code, and provides essential licensing details.](https://copyleaks.com/academic-integrity)
        * * [GenAI Governance & ComplianceGuarantee ethical AI use and regulatory compliance with a robust and fully scalable governance framework.](https://copyleaks.com/governance-risk-and-compliance)
        * * [Unauthorized LLM UsageEnsure your intellectual property is protected from unauthorized use by large language models (LLMs).](https://copyleaks.com/unauthorized-llm-usage)
        
    * * * [AI Model TrainingEnsure your AI model is trained solely on human-created datasets to enhance accuracy and avoid potential collapse.](https://copyleaks.com/ai-model-training-data)
        * * [IP & CopyrightPreserve your intellectual property from unauthorized use and ensure full copyright compliance.](https://copyleaks.com/ip-and-copyright) 
        * * [Codeleaks Code Governance & ComplianceSecure your intellectual property and maintain code integrity with AI-powered detection.](https://copyleaks.com/code-governance-and-compliance)
        
* Products
    * * * #### Products
                
        * * #### Integrations
                
    * * * [AI DetectorThe only enterprise solution designed to verify whether content was written by a person or AI.](https://copyleaks.com/ai-content-detector)
            * [Plagiarism CheckerInstantly detect plagiarism, paraphrased content, and similar text while verifying originality.](https://copyleaks.com/plagiarism-checker)
            * [Writing AssistantEmpower error-free writing with suggestions on sentence structure, mechanics, word choice, and more.](https://copyleaks.com/writing-assistant)
        * * [API IntegrationAward-winning AI & Plagiarism Detection and Writing Assistance to ensure complete content integrity and transparency.](https://copyleaks.com/api)
            * [LMS IntegrationThoroughly scan for multiple forms of plagiarism, AI-generated content, and more from your educational organization’s LMS.](https://copyleaks.com/learning-management-systems)
            * [Browser ExtensionVerify what a human wrote and what is AI-generated with the AI Detector Browser Extension.](https://copyleaks.com/ai-content-detector/extension)
* Resources
    * * * #### Resources

    * * * [About usMeet the Copyleaks leadership team and learn about our mission and values.](https://copyleaks.com/about-us)
        * * [News & MediaThe latest Copyleaks announcements, updates, news and media features.](https://copyleaks.com/about-us/media)
        * * [AI Testing MethodologiesExplore the various testing methodologies used to assess the accuracy of the AI Detector.](https://copyleaks.com/ai-content-detector/testing-methodology)
        * * [Help CenterGet the support you need for integration, platforms, dashboards, and more.](https://help.copyleaks.com/)
        * * [
                
                ](https://copyleaks.com/blog/what-is-gemini-ai-and-how-does-it-work)

                [
                
                ](https://copyleaks.com/blog/the-process-of-ai-prompt-generation)

    * * * #### Learn
                
    * * * [Success StoriesExplore how Copyleaks has empowered clients to protect content, ensure originality, and adopt AI responsibly.](https://copyleaks.com/case-studies)
        * * [TestimonialsDiscover why some of the world’s largest businesses, educational institutions, and millions of individuals trust Copyleaks.](https://copyleaks.com/testimonials)
        * * [The Original Source PodcastJoin Copyleaks COO, Shouvik Paul, as he engages with leading industry experts on the latest trends in AI, EdTech, plagiarism, and more.](https://copyleaks.com/the-original-source-podcast)
        * * [BlogYour resource for learning about the best plagiarism practices, latest findings, and more.](https://copyleaks.com/blog)
* [")
    
    ")
    
    English (United States)](# "English (United States)")
    
    [")
    
    ")
    
    English (United States)](# "English (United States)") [

    Arabic](https://copyleaks.com/ar/privacy-policy/ "Arabic") [")
    
    ")
    
    Chinese (China)](https://copyleaks.com/zh/privacy-policy/ "Chinese (China)") [")
    
    ")
    
    French (France)](https://copyleaks.com/fr/privacy-policy/ "French (France)") [

    German](https://copyleaks.com/de/privacy-policy/ "German") [

    Hindi](https://copyleaks.com/hi/privacy-policy/ "Hindi") [

    Italian](https://copyleaks.com/it/privacy-policy/ "Italian") [

    Japanese](https://copyleaks.com/ja/privacy-policy/ "Japanese") [

    Russian](https://copyleaks.com/ru/privacy-policy/ "Russian") [")
    
    ")
    
    Spanish (Spain)](https://copyleaks.com/es/privacy-policy/ "Spanish (Spain)") [

    Turkish](https://copyleaks.com/tr/privacy-policy/ "Turkish") [")
    
    ")
    
    Portuguese (Portugal)](https://copyleaks.com/pt/privacy-policy/ "Portuguese (Portugal)")

[Home](https://copyleaks.com/) 〉 **Privacy Policy**

Privacy Statement
=================

Last revised December 13, 2022

INTRODUCTION
------------

This Privacy Statement (“Statement”) is incorporated into and is a part of the Copyleaks Ltd. Terms of Use (“Terms”). Capitalized terms used herein and not defined shall have the meanings set forth in the Terms. We have developed the following Statement to protect our customers and inform everyone how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to your use of our Website located at http://copyleaks.com and any other website we use or shall use in the future, in connection with the Service (“Site”). We at Copyleaks strongly respect the right to privacy of our customers. We collect and process information in computerized systems for the purposes set out below, including to provide our Services and to protect our legitimate interests. Our collection and processing of your information is in accordance with the Israeli Privacy Protection Law, 5741-1981 (the “Protection of Privacy Law”) and any other legal and regulatory provisions that apply to us. By using the Service (the “Service” or “We/Us/Our”), you (“you” or “user”) consent to the privacy practices described in this Statement.

We reserve the right to change this privacy statement and we may update it from time to time, as necessary and according to the changes in any applicable law.

PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT ABOUT THE USER
-------------------------------------------------------

**Information you give us:** We collect any information that you submit to us (“Personal Information”):

* In the sign up and setup sections of the Site, we will collect your name, country, company, username, e-mail address, user type (teacher, student etc.), and, if you so choose, the content that you submit for a scan.
* When content you upload contains Personal Information, or when you enter any Personal Information into any postings or comments within the Service, we will collect such information and this information too. Personal Information in content you submit will only be visible to another user if it is identical or similar to the content that other user submitted.
* When you leave us feedback or request support, we will collect any information that is contained in your feedback or support request.
* When you contact us by e-mail or telephone, using any of the e-mail addresses or telephone numbers provided on the Site, we collect any Personal Information you may provide to us voluntarily in connection with this communication.

**Information required for the payment:** Personal Information required for payment is collected by our payment processors, under their terms.

**Cookies:** We also collect information through cookies as explained below.

BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE WHATSOEVER, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER.

USE OF INFORMATION
------------------

All information obtained from your registration process is for the use of Copyleaks only. This information is collected to manage the accounts of Copyleaks users, to improve the content of the Services and to fulfill any transactions, enhance the operation of the Services, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyse use of the Services, improve our product and Services offerings, provide you with updates about our products and Services, provide support, send you notices about our Privacy Statement and Terms and enforce our Terms. No collected information is divulged or sold to any third party (except for possible use of third-party email and postal mailing Services conducting business on behalf of Copyleaks). To provide the Services, Copyleaks will process the content that you provide, in connection with your use of the Services. Please note that if such content contains personal information, this information may also be processed and disclosed to other users for the purpose of providing the Service and as an inherent part of it. We may also use all information we obtained from any source to comply with any legal requirements and judicial and governmental orders, issued by national or foreign authorities, if we believe we are required to comply with them. We may use and transmit the information according to the applicable law. The term “applicable law” in this paragraph also includes orders from governmental organizations and courts (national and foreign). Subject to the law, we may transfer information as part of the sale of our business (including in the negotiations of such sale), and within the framework of a reorganization, merger, joint ventures and other transactions related to our business. In such a case, the recipient of the information will be subject to the same restrictions on the use of information to which we are subject. In accordance with the law, we may sometimes transfer aggregate information to third parties for various purposes, such as research or for the purposes of those parties. In these cases, we will take steps to make this information transfer in a manner that makes it difficult to identify you or others.

DATA PRIVACY
------------

We understand that the data you send to Copyleaks is confidential and treat it as such. Except as otherwise provided in this Statement, we will never share the data you send us with anyone unless required by law. Access will be restricted to the team members you invite, and to certain Copyleaks staff in order to provide support and develop the service.

MEDIA, ADVERTISEMENTS AND DIRECT MAILING
----------------------------------------

When you provide us with your contact details, you agree that we may contact you and send you mail and advertisements regarding our Services. We may create a profile to serve your better targeted advertisements. We may contact by e-mail, telephone, mobile phone (including SMS messages), social networks and other means. To stop receiving commercial communications, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://copyleaks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). You may still receive service-related communications.

RIGHT TO REVIEW AND CORRECT INFORMATION
---------------------------------------

You may review the Personal Information we have about you on our website. If the information we hold about you is incorrect, you have the right to request its correction or deletion.

RIGHT TO WITHDRAW YOUR CONSENT AND TO HAVE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION DELETED
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Applicable law may give you additional rights, such as to withdraw your consent to process your Personal Information; to have it deleted; to object to processing (for example, when the processing is based on the legitimate interest of Copyleaks and you believe that your rights prevail over it). To receive more information or make any request, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://copyleaks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We will review your request in accordance with your and our rights (such as the right to keep information for protection from legal claims) and obligations (such as the duty to store information for tax purposes) under the applicable laws, notify you of the results of this review, and act accordingly. We may, however, not be able to continue to serve you. To delete content you submitted, please go to: [https://copyleaks.com/Manage/RemoveFromInternalDB](https://copyleaks.com/Manage/RemoveFromInternalDB)

SECURITY
--------

We follow appropriate industry standards to protect information which is in our possession, according to the applicable law. For this purpose, we use reasonable security measures which comply with the standards of the Internet industry, including encryption and other protections. We have adopted strict measures for the protection of privacy and the confidentiality of the information which safeguard against errors in the use of information provided by you or against unauthorized access to such information. Despite the aforementioned, there is a risk of unauthorized access to our database. In that case, so long as we have used reasonable security measures, we will not be liable for damages caused by such unauthorized access or for the transfer of Information to a third party due to such access.

SECURITY COOKIES AND AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION
----------------------------------------------

In order to improve our services and our website, we use a technology called cookies, which are text files placed on your computer by a web server. The cookies are not a computer program and cannot read information or perform any actions. The cookies we use, as well as other similar technologies helps us to improve your browsing experience and our service to you, to improve the security of our website. Please note that we may use third party cookies to collect usage and statistical information which does not include personally identifiable information. You may block cookies at any time by changing your browsing setting or by withdrawing your consent (as describe above), except for operational and security Cookies which are necessary for the proper functioning of our website.

BROWSER USE
-----------

Note that in the ordinary course of internet activity, certain information may be sent from your browser to third parties. We have no control over the information sent from your browser to such third parties and recommends that you ensure that your browser settings prevent the disclosure of information you would like to keep confidential.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
-----------------------

Our provision of the Service which enables you to access third party services or links to other websites or locations (“Third Party Services”) is for your convenience only and does not signify our endorsement of such Third Party Services, other websites, locations or their contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these Third Party Services or outside websites or their content. This Statement does not apply to these Third Party Services or outside websites. We strongly recommend that you learn about the privacy and security practices and policies of Third Party Services before providing them with any personal information.

CONTACT US
----------

If you have any questions or comments about this Statement or the practices relating to the Site, or wish to correct, delete, or update any Personal Information we have collected, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://copyleaks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will make an effort to reasonably respond to your inquiry, or to update or remove any personal information you have provided us as indicated by you.

Our assigned Data Protection Officer is Alon Yamin.  
Any notifications of claimed copyright infringement must be sent to our Data Protection Officer:  
Alon Yamin  
Copyleaks Inc  
115 East 23rd St, 7th floor  
New York, NY 10010  
Email: [\[email protected\]](https://copyleaks.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Table of Contents

115 E 23rd St., 7th Fl  
New York, NY 10010

[

](https://copyleaks.com/compliance-certifications#soc2)

[

](https://copyleaks.com/compliance-certifications#pci)

Solutions

Products

Integrations

Company

Resources

[Manage Cookies](javascript:void(0))

[")

")

English (United States)](# "English (United States)")

[")

")

English (United States)](# "English (United States)") [

Arabic](https://copyleaks.com/ar/privacy-policy/ "Arabic") [")

")

Chinese (China)](https://copyleaks.com/zh/privacy-policy/ "Chinese (China)") [")

")

French (France)](https://copyleaks.com/fr/privacy-policy/ "French (France)") [

German](https://copyleaks.com/de/privacy-policy/ "German") [

Hindi](https://copyleaks.com/hi/privacy-policy/ "Hindi") [

Italian](https://copyleaks.com/it/privacy-policy/ "Italian") [

Japanese](https://copyleaks.com/ja/privacy-policy/ "Japanese") [

Russian](https://copyleaks.com/ru/privacy-policy/ "Russian") [")

")

Spanish (Spain)](https://copyleaks.com/es/privacy-policy/ "Spanish (Spain)") [

Turkish](https://copyleaks.com/tr/privacy-policy/ "Turkish") [")

")

Portuguese (Portugal)](https://copyleaks.com/pt/privacy-policy/ "Portuguese (Portugal)")

All rights reserved. Use of this website signifies your agreement to the [Terms of Use](https://copyleaks.com/termsofuse).
